{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","address":"13331 Fourteenth","zipcode":"48238","owner":"GjeLosh Dedvukaj","licenseNumber":"035638","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000044755E566DC754C080A530B28E324540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44943","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"139","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Front counter","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"In the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"44943","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"cockroaches","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-02-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"43196","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"4","pfcount":"2","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"In the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":" after handling soiled equipment, surfaces, utensils","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Water heater","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water source/system to meet demand."},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"At the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Rear door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grill","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43196","inspectionDate":"6/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"In the Restroom(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41766","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2018-03-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41766","inspectionDate":"3/16/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Wall (South)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41169","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2018-01-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41169","inspectionDate":"1/4/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"41169","inspectionDate":"1/4/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"cockroaches","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"41144","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2017-12-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41144","inspectionDate":"12/19/2017","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41144","inspectionDate":"12/19/2017","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"cockroaches","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"inspectionid":"41144","inspectionDate":"12/19/2017","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40578","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"2","pfcount":"4","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"At the Front counter","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"In the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40578","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"4-703.11","violationDescription":"After being cleaned, EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be SANITIZED  by an approved process.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not immersed in","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Completely submerse equipment/utensil."}]},{"inspectionid":"38843","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2017-05-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38843","inspectionDate":"5/31/2017","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"38843","inspectionDate":"5/31/2017","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Freezer (chest)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"38700","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2017-05-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38700","inspectionDate":"5/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Routine inspections","subItem":"of premises for evidence of pests","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On the floor Pest droppings","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Inspections must be performed as stated above."}]},{"inspectionid":"36693","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","inspectionDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"2","pfcount":"3","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Water source and system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water source/system to meet demand."},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"restroom","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"in public restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"36693","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1456","name":"Grandy's Coney Island Restaurant","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1456"}}